A good friend to meet, MBC
It's a true story
I even crossed the icy road
Missing the car means this
Is this real?
Ah, a taxi will come soon.
Let's just walk
Ah, I'm crazy about twenty degrees, sister.
Dongwon's embrace
Uh, waiting for a taxi
How can I count my legs like that while making deliveries?
Money is the scariest thing
In the future, in the world
I know how it will change
Are you spending that much money?
How does the world change?
decentralization
financial
Virtual wallet in the future
One, anywhere, freely
A world where we can trade will come
You and me too
digital assets
I'm going to make a fuss to get it
You guys like this
I won't invest
economy
Sister, I want to be excluded from the market.
You will be left out
This isn't gambling
They said it was one room and I asked what they meant.
Oh, it's gambling
Whether it's Ong Bak
Let's not work hard on things that don't work, yeah
this edition
here
Either fold it or keep it for real.
I'll have to watch
What did you guys have? Yeah, yeah
No, he said he would watch over whatever he had.
But what do you have?
young beauty
Uh shining intelligence um
skin
um
I have a little bit of that savings
Geummyeon yes
sincere effort
To me too
I have an asset called hard work.
Wipe away your tears and talk, I won’t cry.
No, really, what are you doing like this?
What should I do?
Ah
Then why should you really try it?
Yeah
That's that
Coin, how do you do that?
That's it
watermelon
applause
towel
health
uh puppy puppy
Ji
map city
poetry
I can't remember
Will you wait just a moment, quickly, quickly?
poetry
I don't like it, yeah
You're going
This is the first time you appear in my dream
If you finish everything,
You're just going to go.
don't go
I can't think of my mom yet. Um.
poetry
Words that start with sisa
child charm watch market downtown seed
No, you know
What's coming now at the end
It's not the right time. Sid has robbed everything.
Juni’s timing wasn’t bad.
The other friends are still there
When it's the last time, everyone coins together
You'll have to use it as a user
What does this mean?
Timing is everything
Once you get to the fixed point,
Because I will tell you everything
Then don't worry
Go quickly
Because now is the real beginning
We plan to honor that contribution.
Here's the news
Recently, the domestic financial market
Without being able to find a clear path
Virtual currency replaces
It is attracting attention like an investment.
In fact, KOSPI and won dollar
The exchange rate fell together
KOSPI index is based on closing price
Two thousand four hundred
Repeating the rise and fall along the line
Stuffy box ticket
We are continuing the flow
In a situation like this
Including Enderion
in front of some virtual
In the sports
The atmosphere of anticipation for a new beginning
It's being detected
Changes in stagnant market conditions
Could it be a signal?
Gyuchu attracts attention
This is my starting sports short story.
Lee Sang-ho is two thousand eighteen
PyeongChang Winter Olympics
wake up wake up
You're the doormat
Take it easy and let me fix it.
That's right, you
The girl is so fearless
I sleep with the door open like that.
I'm falling asleep
Dad, why did you come here first?
Lady, it's late, oh, it's late, oh my gosh
Oh my
The fat spores are like this.
Let's be patient
I have to endure it
you are not a beast
Get your baby down every now and then.
This is my kid who gave me all the training for the game.
Hehehehehehe
You little crow
Oh, how long has it been since I went in?
crawl out
Ah, there is no threshold in the bathroom. Shower
too long
If you do this, the water will overflow.
Why aren't you cleaning?
Hey, there’s no threshold on the front door over there.
Hey there
All the dust from outside comes inside.
Is this just a one-off because I have no concept?
Oh, that's right
Would he really come and do this without even contacting me?
uh
I'll be there soon
I stopped by on my way to the hospital.
hospital yes
waist
Ah ah
so painful
Don't just answer the survey.
I want you to get proper treatment.
you get married
Don't you do it?
suddenly what
Why does mom always
The conversation starts before we get married.
You live like this
Quickly before Byeongjun finds out.
Getting married
Let’s start with the food so the kids can’t even eat.
mom
Mom, maybe
I have a legacy to pass on to me.
Either that or that
That chamber pot lying around in the warehouse
genuine luxury goods
If you go out, you'll make a loud noise
This is what you receive
Was I the only one who didn't know that?
What are you talking about?
You need money to get married
I don't have any money or anything
Who said they were going to marry me?
Was it a car?
It was a car
This kind of bastard
no where
How dare you take my baby, where is my baby?
Because it’s not enough
money
I don't have enough money
Mr. Lee
Eat and go out
Still, it was my birthday and seaweed soup was
have to eat
You can't look like your dad though.
If it's not enough, it's not enough
All you have to do is live hard
You know
Your dad is terminally ill.
It's dead and I can't fix it even if I wake up.
My father was a sick person.
Jackpot bottle
yes
I need to raise a cow
Without a decent job or fashion
one shot of life
Dreaming of hitting the jackpot
One day, my father, who was concentrating on business,
He said he would raise cows.
dad said
Return to the ship that grew up listening to classical music
Things like red ginseng are big
It's making money
Then I
I grew up listening to K-pop
I want to raise a cow
Fans sing the song their brother sang
I grew up listening to it
How many cows will you buy and eat?
But
Awesome
her brother's drugs
Fans who heard the news of the medication
I grew up listening to his songs
of our cattle
I started to question my sanity
it involves him
Boycott of all products
led to exercise
Business goes smoothly
ruined
Dad didn't stop yeah
I need to go to space
My in-laws' cousin is the Chinese national anthem.
I work at a space industrial base.
The father I knew
I fell into a dream once again
Using the external materials of the rocket
I'm going to build a caravan
But
Wow, awesome
The rocket in question launches
A scene where a fire breaks out in ten seconds
It is broadcast in real time
Business is ruined once again
I'll come back successful
Until daddy can't be fucked any more
ruined
Dad is that guy
After leaving home, determined to succeed,
we have
I survived each day through hardships.
Yes, it's here. It's here. Yes.
Be careful
Hey this is fucking
then I
That was the only thought
Don't live like your dad
A life like a coin is not even a dream
Don't dream
IC
Even though you promised so much, are you still buying this?
You crazy bitch, did you call my Max B?
Oh, I'm surprised.
I didn't call you
Ah
quickly
I need to sell this quickly or something.
Haha thank you dad yes
come early today
Yes, take care.
Mr. Dahye
Oh, I just happened to meet you here.
Good morning hahaha
The weather isn't too refreshing, yeah
There was a time when the morning on the way to work was refreshing
Unless you get shot in the head
I brought you coffee. Please drink this.
Ah
Thank you. Let’s go in now.
Deal with it
Deal with it, deal with it
Guarantee the right to survive
Guarantee, guarantee, guarantee
Take responsibility for employment succession
Take responsibility, take responsibility, shit writing
It tastes good and yes
From my twenties to my eighties
Age group
Our snacks that can encompass
The name is easy
I think it should be intuitive
chicken
Identity made based on
To clearly emphasize
It tastes good
Tasty chicken taste
I understand the meaning of snacks this well.
Is there another name that contains it?
um
Was this too absurd?
I'm not bored
There is a degree of intuitiveness.
Yes more like this
Creative and somewhat artistic
Wouldn't it need a name?
There must be something better
Tackle only
Then don't call and tell Daehan too.
Then maybe something
Is there any other
What if you put
yes
By adding silver
Just change the survey.
It tastes good
When you eat sweets, they taste good.
I feel better
In the sense of killing two birds with one stone.
no
It's good to change one survey, yes.
That's for sure
investigation
I feel so much better when I change one thing
I think it’s become fresher, right?
Yes, the taste is good
It also means better
Ah, Dahee, your sense is killing me.
Ahahahaha
Ah, whose motive is this?
That's great, that's fourteen
fourteen
No, let's go and win
Oh yes yes yes
yes
Dahee, why are you there?
Ah, but Dahye
How many seeds did you have, senior?
Twelfth Year, Thirteenth Year
Oh, I
I don't think I've seen you before
Sorry, I'm here
My feet are hurt a little
Ha, I'll go over there and rest.
respectful
Dear executives and employees
beautiful season
welcome fall
Everyone gathered in one place
It's very meaningful
Excuse me, can I sit here?
on the record player
Because we put it in each of our classmates’ seats.
we came back together
looking at the egg
here is my place
towards the future
new plan
The only place to sleep is here
There will be
I'm sorry
there
What are you doing? Sit down quickly.
Ah
uh what
I made a chair that didn't exist
You're a total creative genius.
Nothing special
It's simple
Just hold on and hold on
That's how I endured it
I lasted three days and nights
Hold on until you die
Hold on until the tears dry up
Those tears
Hold on until it's over
Hold on until the end
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on
That's how I endured it
Uh uh ah ah
uh
That day I was that transparent
sit in the chair and
Foresaw an uncertain future
The sadness that lies ahead of Private Private House
Another sad future
And the sad premonition is
Why is it not wrong?
Now, the names that came out today are
Let's put him up as a candidate.
Yes, I did it.
Dahye and Tonggol
Our Children's Day Promotion Opportunity
Final for the two of you
You have been selected as a candidate
Oh really
If everything goes well this time
Highway all the way to Daeri
You know it's burning
Well, for three years
I applied every time, but every time
Contest that drank water
That's it
I got this chance in my life
This is a true story
Comrade Mr.
Why aren't you saying anything?
I like it or I don’t like it
Comrade Mr.
That uh uh
Awesome, awesome hahaha let’s organize it.
Okay
uh pocket
What's going on? What's going on?
They say there is a sunrise in the hole too.
ok let's go
Dahye Jeong, let's get promoted
Hehehe
Mr. Jisung
Yes, can you give me a copy? Yes.
Oh Ji-seong
Yes, please take this to the sales team. Yes.
Mr. Jisung
Please set your face, yes.
Just one cup of coffee
Bird Hawk Stumbles
The shoes are pretty and you are pretty too.
Yes, my mom’s new product, Shinjji.
I guess I bought Jaeseong’s shoes. Yes, they are pretty.
But even if you report something like that, it becomes a problem.
yes
I couldn't work after reporting something like that.
Well, well
Mr. Jisung
Why is it because I don’t do much?
How much do I have to glue during Yeongsu?
There are a lot
But these shoes are more comfortable than they look
Ah, but
That kind of paste
If you just do the same thing
I'm not anxious
No, I came through a public recruitment process like this too.
I have a lot of worries
How much more will Mr. Jisong do?
Because I want to
um
It's me
So I don’t think it will increase.
Why don't you worry
no what
What if you worry about that?
I'm only getting older
Oh, of course
Someday I too
Do you worry about things like Mr. Cho?
But the time will come
Oh, I'm scared just thinking about that
Ha, what should I worry about?
Wrinkles
That's not what you said
Oh my
Oh, I'm sorry. Of course I
It's not like that.
sorry sorry sorry
Sorry about that
I have wrinkles. Look at them.
Oh my oh my
Min Sang, you must not enter that compartment.
Oh what is this
It's been like that since yesterday
Oh, I really didn't know how I was deceived
No, but why don’t you clean it up?
The people who clean like that are on strike.
You're in the middle of it.
Uh uh wow and that.
uh
It can't be done by removing it, it has to be drilled through.
no
I have no taste for food
I haven't been able to eat since lunch yesterday
I really can't eat that.
Oh my, Eunsam, what are you doing?
Hey, don’t do that, Eunsam.
To those at work
lunch
What pleasure is there if you take away time?
I can't ruin it because of this shit.
Mr. Eunsam
What's inside
Don’t be disturbed even if you hear a sound.
stay away
No no what kind of kid is this
Die, Mr. Jeong Sang
die
Mr. Sang-sang, it’s okay.
uh
Let's see what to see
Oh, when did you come?
He's a really scary person today
How did that happen?
Uh uh uh poison trick
Oh, I ate it when I was spinning.
I think the mood will improve.
Ah
Well, guys, let’s go get something to eat.
Ugh, I’m running out of food right now.
I will live
He said he would leave so we could get some water.
Yay
get out of the way
Come on, come on.
I will eat well
um
A line
Ah
no
What's going on
Jjansuni spends this much money
Who are these bastards?
Whose foot is that on my lap?
Yeah ah
Sorry
It's great to do some stretching.
AC
It's because my feet hurt. It's because of the iron shoes.
Steel shoes are less expensive
You bought shoes um
salty
FW Season Limited Color
Hmm, it's pretty
Yeah, how much is it?
Well it's strange
Why did I have to pay rent?
Will there be a new product coming out?
It's your monthly rent
This is it
The price makes sense for your situation, sister.
I wish I lived according to my means
I'm over there at Seoul Station
Go and sleep with Mr. Kim.
Go to church over there and it’s free.
I have to survive by receiving school meals.
Then live like that
This girl can't do it.
I went to Buddhist kindergarten.
ha
Hey, you spend that much
If you don't want to be a luxury
I know what to do
How do I do it? How do I do it?
I need to increase my income
So how do you get that income?
No way, hey, it’s about coins again.
Ah but you
Right away that day
I asked about this and that as if I was going to try it.
why is there no news
Ah, that, ah, sister
Oh, I think Dayeon is like an older sister.
I turn my eyes to that kind of day school
coin
Can you find someone who would do the same thing?
Right, sister
uh uh
uh
Yeah, I tend to be a bit like that.
Yeah no
I'm crazy if I do this even though I can't make any money.
But I earn it
You guys earn like this
You’re buying me something delicious too, right?
Come on, gather around
Are you by any chance?
I've heard of the Jake Cub.
Jay Curve
Even if it seems like it will fall endlessly
Someday I'll sell the upward curve
That's J-Curve
Well, it's kind of like a pattern.
The flow is perfect now
It's like this, um
It's like a diet.
um
Although it may seem like a policy at first,
If you diet and exercise consistently, someday you will
It means losing weight, right?
Now look, look, yeah
You can make money this is Jay
I'm accepting it, yeah
Ah
What does this mean?
Now hit rock bottom
The only thing left to do is go up.
really
The best
Sell drugs haha yeah
Il-in, what are you doing?
Jisung, I understand.
Oh Jisung, Kim Jisung
Oh, I understand.
Oh, when will I become Jay?
It's not a child
This is not the time, let's work like this
Dahye, I had lunch. Ah, yes.
Ah, looks like they're preparing a PT.
Ah ah
But this PT
Who is doing the judging?
Well, with the directors
Dr. Han
Ha so good
Isn’t your expression too transparent?
a handsome person
When I think of it
I have a disease that makes me happy
Hey, but
Who is Dr. Han?
Ah
Yejin, I’m not sure because she’s an intern.
There is
Our director and the protagonist of the remaining snow
You know that too, chocolate cake
that's for now
It's our company's most popular item.
There were a lot of concerns before the release.
The company's first product in nearly three years
Because it’s a new statue
Ah, what should I do to sell well?
Ah, what should I do to sell better?
Hey really
Each vice-president
I had a crazy meeting.
This guy doesn't have an answer.
Wait a minute
right then
Dr. Han, who was quiet the whole time, said
Just one line
aka
conscience line
Are you buying snacks?
Consumers who don’t know if they are buying nitrogen
The era of Kim Han-tae's gangster
Where is it
Look at this ah
A line has been drawn
Up to this line
I will definitely fill you up with snacks.
aka
Good conscience, this is what Dr. Han said.
I ignored it as much as Dr. Han.
chic
As soon as this idea was released
It caused a huge stir
But
This marketing really hit the jackpot
It was because of what happened last time
yes this opponent
There wasn't enough rotation
No points were deducted.
This is plain
It's just a judgment
I can't see it
Yes, but then
The unexpected doping happened
uh uh gold medal
gold medal gold medal
Oh, I carried the gold medal
I carried the gold medal
Thanks to you, it was a silver medal
Korean players
I confidently regained my gold medal.
are you watching
Conscience
Our conscience is hidden
If you do this, the whole universe will
I guess I can see that I'm helping Dr. Han.
As if receiving the energy of the universe,
I think he came down to the ground.
So this is
The legend of Park Hyeok-got awakened below
It's the same thing haha
It means you don't have children.
You're a great person.
But why is he a doctor?
Do you have a Ph.D.
Well, that's true too
It's been such a hit since I was a regular employee.
You planned a lot of products.
Ah, from then on, the real boss
Oh my, Dr. Han
our doctor
Really what
Come like my own grandchild
The floating started, that’s right.
And when you were promoted to general manager,
I am such a strict person to the company.
I want a rank system
You said no, so
Now naturally
The name ‘Dr. Han’ has become established.
Wow, you really are a great person.
Ah
But I saw Dahye during the interview.
I didn't do that
Oh um yes yes
But how will you remember me?
It's just like that
Because Da-hye is the warm type.
Wow, what kind of thing?
Throw a nuclear ball without warning
Oh, it looks a little broken haha. It's okay.
yes
But
Well, he seems like a great person.
something
An insurmountable feeling
It's time to go to the general meeting.
I guess something good happened
From morning onwards
He hummed the song
It's me, yes
Oh, I see.
No, what is this?
It keeps getting stuck in my mouth.
Mr. too-too-too-too-too-too-too-bad
uh what
This is not our inventory list
Mr. Oh left it behind.
Huh oh it's true
Oh, please call Manager Oh. Ah, yes.
Ha, I'm not accepting it.
Manager Oh
You didn't even bring a laptop.
Ah, Oh Dae-ri, quickly find out where you went.
Since you just left, I
Right away
Mr. Jisung
Jisung, hurry up and chase after him.
Oh, wear those comfortable shoes
to
Oh assistant manager, assistant manager
Assistant Manager, Assistant Manager
uh
teacher me
sorry
I'll just pass by once
yes thank you
Oh, assistant manager
Assistant Manager Go
Assistant manager uh ah
Ah
Ah ah
again
Ah
Assistant manager
Oh Ji-seong
Ugh
Hehe yes hehe hehe
Ah ah
Jisung, are you following me now?
Ah
Hello
Uh, Mr. Jisung
I spoke to Oh Dae-ri on the phone.
The documents were in the bag.
I think I should come back to work
Oh my oh my
Ah
Jisung, are you okay?
uh
That
On my way today
a few toes
I feel like I fell
Yes, can you find it for me?
I'm fussing over something that's nothing
I'm getting criticized for things like that.
one one two three
Ah
uh uh
A proper apology, ugh.
I can't move my fingers
Oh my sister
Call a taxi, please call me a call taxi
Hey, the house
How do I call a taxi when it’s right in front of me?
Oh oh really
Ah, I can't walk the starting jump.
Ah ah ah
Ah ah ah ah ah
Ah ah ah, that's that, that's ah ah ah
Ah
Hey
It's a lie that you eat a solar eclipse every day.
How about eating meat every day?
Don't say it, you guys
Oh, managers
Please save me, this chief priest.
I laughed so hard yeah
guest
Can I accept the catch with my life?
You'll lose
Now, this too is a memory
Here's a picture of us like this
Let's take a picture
Now, one, two, three, smile
Die Mr. Lee
Hey, you're really out of your mind.
Just throw it away
Oh no
Why do you throw away your intelligence?
Oh sir
Very moved
He should also do coins together.
Hey, I'm so annoying
kid gnome coin coin
child
If you like it that much, do it alone.
Why do you keep saying let’s do it together?
I can't do it alone
Oh why why can't I do it
sister
What should I do?
Uh uh I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I'm sorry
Oh sister
It's okay
I don't think I can see
You guys are falling down
If you live like this
Is there anything worse than this?
All I can do is collapse
in our life
Is there anything else left to talk about?
I can't pretend not to know even though I obviously know
Those who don't make that much money
Oh, I hate you, sister, be careful, be careful.
salty
ها
نرى في الحفاظ على عشرات قوية مع
مارون في المستقبل ان شاء الله
A good partnership with Maronjae in the future
You say you want to keep it
Thank you very much
We would like to ask you to please take care of us.
I'll do my best
thank you
TV, wait a minute.
TV over there
I have reserved now
I got a call from the restaurant.
The refrigerator suddenly breaks down
Just give me an hour
I suddenly asked if I could do less.
Hey then what should I do
nearby
I need to find another restaurant quickly.
No, I tried to do that
It's Islam
another day restaurant
It will take some time to find it again
Beef rib house
The meat restaurant is smokey
Face each other due to suction
It'll be hard to see and talk about.
What should I do then?
Hit this
What should I do with my child?
I have to tell my child.
Oh, that's right
Please follow me
La la la la la la la
Is this a restaurant?
I want to serve appetizers.
arbitizer yes
Marron's family
To the world using our products
only one
a special appetizer
I want to make it for you
If marronje is a product
Can that happen with cookies?
Okay, so what you see now is
Popular products of our maron confectionery
This is a milk card.
on this for a long time
Sweet peach released
Add a spoonful of jam
And this
All you have to do is rotate the lens for just 40 seconds.
The milk tart peach tart is completed.
um
When was this popsicle bar released?
Over 100,000 units sold in one day
This is Kkriba.
Open this and fill it with ice
Please add it to carbonated water
You can drink while working
Delicious non-alcoholic
The cocktail is ready
Wow Rajjiden
They say it’s very delicious.
Isn't it really cute?
Now, finally, the cookie taste
Ice cream and marron jaggery pepe stick
benzbenz
and soon
Marron Confectionery's special product scheduled to be released
talent
It stops when you aim for a chocolate marshmallow.
No
At our Maron Confectionery,
Certified in one day
I am using whoopi gelatin
Lalalalala
Oh my, this thorn
I think you should go
This meal restaurant is ready.
Let's go, yeah
meal meal
yes i got it
Eunsang
Thank you for your hard work today
Yes, the buyer is Eunsang.
You praised me a lot.
I plan to visit the company again next year.
Even then, Eunsang
He asked if he could see me again.
Of course
no yes
I'm anxious about tomorrow right now
What do you promise about next year?
Oh, then you can leave the company.
Oh, that's a shame
I think he's someone I can't live without in this company.
I don't know
That's the same for everyone
Let’s look at the right to action.
Let's see. Let's see.
Let's see and do the succession of Wooyong.
Next time, you should go next time. Yes, yes.
Ah, maybe
When you leave
Do you have other plans?
Do you ask yes
I'm going
Odile
Hey there
to the moon
let's go
A major holiday in the distribution industry
Let's go to Children's Day
Marron Daegwa's Best Seller Chocolate Cup
And the children's president
Yongki Cartoon Character Yongkiwa
There were a lot of chocolate cups
Ah, um
Yongki’s signature white beads and
Added white chocolate
Yongki’s Special Edition
To special edition
children
Excuse me
uh
Oh Dahye, what are you doing here?
No, didn’t you get off work earlier?
Oh, leave that umbrella behind.
Are you preparing for PT?
Yeah well it's just okay
People who work overtime should eat it.
I brought you some coffee.
Dahye, please have a drink too.
Ah
thank you
No
Do your best in preparing for PT, fighting!
But
Da-hye, make sure to prepare PT.
You're talking like someone who doesn't do it.
Oh well, of course I work hard too.
But
Because I did my best
not
Even if it happens, I don’t think it will be disappointing.
If it doesn't work out this time
You can try again next time
Isn't that right?
I'm jealous
yes
Even if I fail
There is room to try again
I'm jealous
No
He said he came to get that umbrella. Oh, that’s right.
Well then, I'll go in first.
See you tomorrow
ha
Mmm uh um um ah
let's go
Children's Day, a major holiday in the distribution industry
Best Seller of Water Chestnuts
A major holiday in the distribution industry
Celebrating Children's Day
Marron Zega's best-selling chocolate cocktail
children's president
As expected, we met
Well then
A representative name in the distribution industry
Eugene's mom is my sweetheart
I’m dying of envy because you’re not going.
I said that
Well then
let's go quickly
You need money to get married
I don't have any money or anything
Who said they were going to marry me?
uh mom
I ate rice
no
waist
Have you received treatment?
Ah, when I wake up, I feel alive.
I just left it alone
No, why leave it alone?
my mom is a doctor
Oh, I told you to go and get proper treatment.
Okay, that's it.
i don't know my body
I have to work. Stop, mom.
hello mom
Oh, it's noisy
Oh, I'm surprised.
Be quiet, ah
What is this guy really?
um
Um heh heh almost done
Okay uh
Long key and chocolate chip meet
Should I give you some icons?
met
Haha
Why?
Who are you and what are you doing?
open the door
Oh my
Oh my oh my oh my oh my
You looked for me earlier
Oh my
Open the door, what are you still doing?
how are you going
open the door
You looked for me earlier
Why are you acting like a bastard?
This is not the fuck
How are you going? Is it true?
Ah
That's my place over there
There is Mr.
What should I do if my laptop breaks?
If the file is deleted, you won't be able to do PT.
If you don't have PT, you can't get promoted.
If you don't get promoted, your salary won't go up.
Then mom
How much money do you need to fix my back?
No, my phone screen is broken right now.
I can't fix it, so what
What does the cell phone sound like?
Wait a minute, cell phone
crazy bitch
Did you call my Maxbee cell phone?
Hi Maxbee, please report it to everyone.
I'll call you one by one
This is an emergency report.
What's going on?
Please save me
Well then, first of all
Let's go together today
내일 다시 연락드리겠습니다
저 새끼
꼭 공권력으로 다스리십시오
안 그럼
제가 사적으로 다스리겠습니다 네
진짜예요
이 언니는 사람을 찢어요
아 네 노력하겠습니다
아 저 그럼
충성 감사합니다
괜찮아
수상하고 있던 파일 다 날아갔어
다시 해야 돼
으흐흐흐
죽어 죽여도 지하철을 타나요
모르겠어 으흐흐
뭐 하는데요
울고만 있으면 밥이 되냐
떡이 되냐
얼른 다시 해야지
이거 궁사체가 나와 명조체가 나
어 어
명조 명조체
나가 얼마나 무서웠는데
아하 이거 왼쪽
정렬이 더 보게 났지 않아
가운데 정렬
가운데 다시 해야 되잖아
개새끼
아
Oh, is this better in blue?
Oh my goodness
Oh well, blue is better.
Ah, sister
Please show some attitude
Let's try to unify it into one.
Is my sister committing suicide now?
We don't know if it's true or not
It's a bit ambiguous.
Then my attitude is
I want to go with Jacob
Yeah
My sister said that
Even if it looks like it's going to fall
In the end, it rises and many things
That's Jacob
me too
At the end of this adversity,
A happy ending is waiting for you
it's my way
How to apply this properly
Try coining
me
I'll work hard
I'm going to work really hard
How are you shaking? Don’t be shaking. Breathe.
Take it out
I'm going to take a deep breath. I can do it. Come on.
Now breathe in
Exhale, inhale, exhale
Science and engineering and one arm
Children's Day Promotion Opportunity
Let's start the presentation
First, Jeongdong-guri
Dahye Jeong will make a presentation.
Byeongman
yes
Ah, Dr. Han
Before you start
Do you have anything to say?
Oh no, let’s get started, kid.
Hmm hmm
A major holiday in the distribution industry
Celebrating Children's Day
Maron Confectionery's best seller chocolate price and
children's president
Yongki met
Children's Day special product
Yongki’s Special Edition
From now on
Let me introduce you in detail.
Children's Day only
Courage specials released
The edition concludes the presentation.
What is it
Is it okay? is it a disaster?
I can't tell just by looking at your expression.
Next, employee Dahee Jeong
I will make a presentation
Oh wait a minute
Is this the end?
Ah
If it's okay with you
Ah, blood
Can I get some feedback?
Oh, if there was something I was missing
I want to know
Because I prepared really hard.
I guess so.
three years ago
You had an interview with me.
yes
I saw it for the first time that day
I thought you were a bit shy, considering.
I remember now
thank you thank you
I'll do my best
I will work really hard
Hey there
yes
Let’s go to the hospital. I’ll do my best.
Haha and then continue
I guess you worked hard ah
thank you
But by then
Doesn’t it have to be a hard process?
Dahye Jeong's results are still
I worked hard
If you do that, it's really like this.
Why don't you want to be open?
Fortunately, congratulations
Ah ah
Nogo
Success let’s go haha, team leader haha
uh
Is Dahye in that mood right now?
Hehehehe
No, what happens when people work?
Sometimes it works and sometimes it doesn't
It happens sometimes.
Well, it didn't work out once.
Make people around you uncomfortable
What can I do to make you notice?
um
Ah
yes
I will also sing a song
Oh okay applause
Senior, you really worked hard.
Yejin, you worked really hard too.
Haha
It's hard to use the internet.
I'm only going to do it for my senior.
After going through all that trouble
in the end
You didn't get accepted because it was a non-public recruitment.
Haha
I guess I have a good hitting feel.
Oh, you touch a lot of bones.
But Yejin
This is not because I am an unofficial recruiter.
no i heard
This PT
It's a game that's being pushed out by public recruiters.
we just
These are people who put you down
us
Except you know everything.
I'm planning to quit after I finish my internship.
I can't do it through unofficial recruitment.
I don't have confidence to go
I also eat rice.
the sky
I'll go in early
Yes, I understand, Dad.
yes
Mr. Dahye
what are you doing here
why did you do that
call your pitch
You told me to cheer up
I was making fun of that.
It's obvious that it won't work anyway.
Did you drink a lot? Are you okay?
No, I'm drunk
yes
Let's get a little more sloppy about my taste.
Why am I the only Americano?
Those other people
Frapeda Latte
Go to the star menu
Tailoring your tastes
Why only me
Buy 10 drinks, get one drink
Chungchungyo thanks to the service provided.
I brought you coffee. Please drink this.
I brought you some coffee.
Dahye, please have a drink too. Wow.
I'm sorry
But Americano
Every time I say something, I don't say anything.
To other people
What are you going to drink every time?
You asked me
Ah
I don't know why I did that either
i know
Why did Dahye do that?
Because
Because I am a person who can do that
So
Pete too
like that
Everyone ignores me so much
They look at me so insignificantly
I'm really sorry, but the coffee
Dahye
I think you really like it
I didn't have a baby
yes it looks like that
Ah, enough to live with a baby
Just like that
Ha, life is hard
I can't see you Dahye
Mr. So more
Even though I'm angry
I'm like this because I'm drunk
Forget it
Mr. Dahye
Still, this PT
Thank you very much for your hard work
Let's try harder in the future
Fighting
If you work hard enough, do whatever it takes.
You just have to live hard
stop
Do your best at PT this week.
Highway all the way to Daeri
Stop it
Even after going through such a hard time
In the end, because it is a non-tolerance
It didn't work out.
I can't work hard
Try harder in the future
us
I won't do it anymore
no sin
I almost hit Da-hye who didn't exist.
Every day
With a falling heart
Three years at a job I’ve endured
My passion is ultimately
I became inferior
Dahye Jeong
You really hit rock bottom.
Wow
Ah, Kang Eun-sang
Oh yeah
Nothing works
There isn't one
You don't have to die
It looks like that, but
In the meantime, something happens.
It's become J-Cub huh
Hey you this
Ha, sister
I
J-Curve in my career
I wanted to be filmed, hehe
But that damn Jay
It gets stuck there.
Ah
My life is at a very low point right now
I'm filming
Even in this tragic moment, there is only one thing
That's what goes up
Did you put in 10,000 won in that damn coin?
I spent a lot of money, oh my
I guess so
Ah
I just don't know
Should I like this?
Should I be angry?
You should like it
That money too
I'm going to someone I like.
why are you angry
I earned 500 won
kid
coin to see this
It was a coin song.
you made it
How much cash do you have now?
I have fifteen hundred won.
I couldn't buy a bottle of detergent
i am proud
Oh really
Well, I earned 500 won with coins.
Now I have 2,000 won
Ah, yes, I understand.
Nothing happens
The fever spreads
That's why he's such a strict person
Hold on and take out your anger
I saw one
Come to your senses, you bitch.
Oh, I'm surprised.
Let’s do PT once
I thought your life would change
It's rice cake
I need money
Whether it’s 500 won or 5 million won
You have to have money so
Life changes
Well, no matter what, I can barely afford this money.
Should I go outside?
Will that money make any difference?
There may be no
Hmm
um
Hmm, is it delicious?
This is
This is definitely
I feel different after eating it.
me
I guess we haven't gone to the sea yet
This is the power of money, did you understand?
Yeah
Ah
Why are you sober because you’re full?
Oh me
After being so harsh towards Da-hye,
What should I do now?
uh
Oh, why does the restaurant hurt?
Did you have an accident?
Oh, I'm surprised.
Oh, that
I came to ask you something.
That song earlier
how do you sing
yes
What song?
The song I just sang at the bar
How do you know that?
It's just a song I like
So how?
That's not even a famous song.
How do you know
No, you might like it
Why can't I like it?
Oh well, that's not it
Oh, I guess you have Hongdae disease.
Yes what
Or
Just me
This song is sung by a singer I want to know.
Either that or
My taste sucks
No, so now I
They even want to judge your tastes.
No, it's not like that.
Oh really
Hey uh
Sorry but
You know next time
As you know, today is for me
Because it's such a hard day
Just work harder next time
that song
How on earth are you doing this?
Just know that
eager
Yes, work hard
But those eyes
These eyes are a bit
Looks like it's turned around
Why are my eyes turning?
Why are you getting closer?
Why why are you coming to me? Why are you coming? Why are you coming?
I'm not working hard
Lalala lalala
let's go
Oh how bad I was yesterday
I guess there really was some kind of accident.
That doctor here
What's going on?
I don't have anything to say. Ta-da.
Ki Hoi wants to go to Beijing.
My mom is a bit harsh.
These days, I've been in touch
I don't think it's going well
It's beautiful
crazy
I earned that much in a really short period of time.
spend more money
Coin uh no
It's okay
I got that ladder because of that money.